so I couldn't record well I got to the
trail walk and had a few ideas now I'm
conscious of the time beyond the trip I
like I like the thought I had before I
left the Pokemon go for Humanity but
finding a way to I love fairy garden I
especially love little fairy doors and
stuff that are in the forest and sound
they just make me happy
keep it as an adult especially for my
four-year-old there's a documentary it's
like a 15 minute small eventually about
a forest somewhere in state that there
was a woman who ruin it for you you see
it there's a person who was putting out
furniture and getting letters or song
and you end up getting in trouble and
have them take it down
so but in doing
doing something similar but it was like
geocaching and that's kind of what
pokemons go was accepted
what creating the geocache what's the
game itself I believe favorite Pokemon
stop getting something to do with very
Gardens where you as the house homeowner
or putting something on the floor that
legal can put a little trinket that has
a light turn over with our call to keep
you see pose where you scan them a
minute knows what you're talking about
when you've got it with your door so
happy in a game where you can search
those out and then scan them and put
them back and having it be interactive
and magical for the kids to find fairies
and get outside and walk and so keep
living on a very flashy old idea but
head two minutes two minutes about we
doubled up the design step that's what I
count with and that is Apple number 81